[
  {
    "Option a": "Unit Testing",
    "Option b": "Integration Testing",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "Which testing is done by developer?",
    "Option c": "Sanity Testing",
    "Option d": "Regression Testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Load Testing",
    "Option b": "Security Testing",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "Which is functional testing?",
    "Option c": "Gorilla Testing",
    "Option d": "Benchmark Testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "SQA",
    "Option b": "SQM",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "Quality Management in software engineering is also known as",
    "Option c": "SQI",
    "Option d": "SQA and SQM "
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Every week",
    "Option b": "After the software has changed",
    "answer": "d",
    "Question": "Select from which of the following regression testing should be performed.",
    "Option c": "As often as possible",
    "Option d": "When the environment has changed"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "When all the tests  run",
    "Option b": "When the  faults have been fixed",
    "answer": "d",
    "Question": "When would the testing have been stopped?",
    "Option c": "When the time completed",
    "Option d": "when all the risk are resolved"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Performance",
    "Option b": "Usability and Security",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "non-functional test does not belong to which of the following categories?",
    "Option c": " State level Transition",
    "Option d": "all of the above"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Security level testing",
    "Option b": "Boundary value analysis",
    "answer": "b",
    "Question": "Which of the following is a form of functional testing?",
    "Option c": "Performance testing",
    "Option d": "Usability testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": " polite and  helpful ",
    "Option b": "Diplomatic",
    "answer": "d",
    "Question": "When reporting faults found to developers, testers should be",
    "Option c": "sensitive and insisting that a bug is not a �\u20AC�feature�\u20AC? if it should be fixed",
    "Option d": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "Option a": " How much regression testing should be done",
    "Option b": "How many more test cases need to written",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "Impact Analysis help to decide which of the following testing describe below.",
    "Option c": "Exit Criteria",
    "Option d": "Different Tools to perform Regression Testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Test Planning ",
    "Option b": "Requirement Analysis",
    "answer": "b",
    "Question": "Select which of the below is not a Fundamental Test Process?",
    "Option c": "implementation and Execution",
    "Option d": "Evaluating test criteria and reporting"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Syntax testing",
    "Option b": " Linear Code Sequence and Jump",
    "answer": "b",
    "Question": "Which of the following techniques is NOT a black box technique?",
    "Option c": "State transition testing ",
    "Option d": "Boundary value analysis"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "User acceptance testing ",
    "Option b": "Component testing",
    "answer": "d",
    "Question": "Select Impact Analysis is used in which of the following?",
    "Option c": "Non-functional system testing",
    "Option d": "Maintenance testing"
  }
]
